{
    "id": "62decfb081844040b6e61f805828ded1",
    "title": "Lay, Lie, Less, Fewer",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A turtle ………………………… many eggs at one time.",
            "description": "Lay means produce or bear. ",
            "answers": [
                "lies",
                "lays",
                "lains"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "165caa27a53e4852b229c6585caebe18"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. the cartons one on top of the other.",
            "description": "To lay something is to put it down carefully.",
            "answers": [
                "Lay",
                "Lie",
                "Lain"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc424adfde514ae29990fc5bad262cec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. the plates on the table.",
            "description": "Laid is the past tense of lay.",
            "answers": [
                "lain",
                "laid",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ca6f1cf4eb34d2e9b61e88f17829677"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry with me because I ……………………… to her.",
            "description": "Lied is the past tense of lie. To lie is to say something untrue.",
            "answers": [
                "laid",
                "lain",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa6c089fccc94d94b3e4d26e785704f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ……………………….. down.",
            "description": "Lie can mean be horizontal.",
            "answers": [
                "lie",
                "lay",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a17fcbceb4a64e539e522c2533a19a1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. down and closed my eyes but I could not sleep.",
            "description": "When lie means be down, lay is its past tense.",
            "answers": [
                "lie",
                "lay",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "274cd8802aa34b86b2d9e83526fced19"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam earns the most money in our family James earns …………………….",
            "description": "The least is the opposite of the most. It is used with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "the least",
                "the lowest",
                "the fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fef73ea9ba4546d38fcc854545e41740"
        },
        {
            "question": "The essay with ………………………. errors is not always the best.",
            "description": "With plural nouns we use fewest and with uncountable nouns we use least.",
            "answers": [
                "the least",
                "the fewest",
                "the lowest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "00baa45f7f974806988f1d5860dd93ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She always arrives when you …………………………. expect it.",
            "description": "When least is used as an adverb, it is used without the.",
            "answers": [
                "least",
                "the least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee2d1f801b5b460390df47929d8728e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………………….. interested in this offer.",
            "description": "Both expressions mean the same. ",
            "answers": [
                "not in the least",
                "not at all",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e6986ce5f575405db6539046c799551a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. people cook their own meals these days.",
            "description": "We use fewer with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Fewer",
                "Less",
                "Lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4ee846c00bb418eada47df6950262e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The most effective way to lose weight is to eat ……………………… food.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative of little.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c0a29b7a5a34969ad2c9f1cafdd328d"
        }
    ]
}